<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PandaFoodFacts</string>
    <string name="title">Welcome to PandaFoodFacts</string>
    <string name="empty"> </string>


    <string name="EcoTitle">Eco-Score: the environmental impact of food products</string>
    <string name="EcoSubtitle1">Why an environmental score?</string>
    <string name="EcoSupport">The Eco-Score is supported by a consortium of many actors committed to better nutrition.</string>
    <string name="EcoSubtitle1a">The Eco-Score, a tool for more sustainable food</string>
    <string name="EcoSubtitle1a1">The Eco-Score helps consumers who wish to move towards a more sustainable diet, by encouraging them to:</string>
    <string name="EcoSubtitle2">What is the Eco-Score?</string>
    <string name="EcoSubtitle3">How is the Eco-Score calculated?</string>
    <string name="EcoSubtitle3a">Life cycle assessment (LCA)</string>
    <string name="EcoSubtitle3a1">Life cycle analysis a standardized assessment method for carrying out a multi-stage environmental assessment and multi-criteria:</string>
    <string name="EcoBody1">Eat less meat but of better quality\nConsume more organic products and products with quality labels\nFavor local and seasonal products, with little packaging\nLimit products containing problematic ingredients (endangered fish, unsustainable palm oil)</string>
    <string name="EcoBody2">The Eco-Score is designed on a model similar to the Nutri-Score: it is a grade from A to E which summarizes 15 environmental impacts. The Eco-Score score is materialized by a colored leaf-shaped logo with a letter from A (very low impact) to E (very high impact).</string>
    <string name="EcoBody3">6 production steps: agriculture, processing, packaging, transportation, distribution and consumption 14 environmental impact indicators: climate change/carbon footprint, ozone layer depletion, ionizing radiation, land, water, and energy use; pollution of air and marine and fresh water (particles, acidification, eutrophication); and depletion of resources.</string>


    <string name="NovaTitle">Nova groups for food processing</string>
    <string name="NovaWhatIs">What is NOVA and how are UPF defined?</string>
    <string name="NovaDefine">The NOVA score measures the level of processing of foods on a scale of 1 “minimally-processed” to 4 “ultra-processed.” Studies have shown that NOVA-4 foods contribute disproportionately to weight gain. For a healthy diet, it is generally recommended to minimize the amount of NOVA-4 foods.</string>
    <string name="NovaElement">Group 1 - Unprocessed or minimally processed foods\nGroup 2 - Processed culinary ingredients\nGroup 3 - Processed foods\nGroup 4 - Ultra-processed food and drink products</string>
    <string name="NovaSubtitle">A classification in 4 groups to highlight the degree of processing of foods</string>
    <string name="NovaBody1">The NOVA classification assigns a group to food products based on how much processing they have been through:</string>


    <string name="moreInfo">Source -> https://nutriscore.blog/</string>
    <string name="moreInfoEco">Source -> https://world.openfoodfacts.org/eco-score-the-environmental-impact-of-food-products/</string>
    <string name="moreInfoNova">Source -> https://us.openfoodfacts.org/nova</string>
    <string name="explication">Basically, the nutritional value for the Nutri-Score letter grade is determined by subtracting the total positive points from the total negative points. And the lower the score, the better the letter grade.</string>
    <string name="tableNutriScore">What Does a Nutri-Score Calculation Look Like?</string>
    <string name="tableLooks">Here’s how the scoring tables look like:</string>
    <string name="nutribody2"> Apicbase does these calculations automatically based on the users recipes in the system and generates the label, giving food production companies an easy way to comply with consumer wishes.</string>
    <string name="nutribody">Nutri-Score — which is an easy-to-understand, colour-coded graphic representation of the quality of nutrients in a product — is, nonetheless, rooted in complex peer-reviewed and science-based nutritional calculations.</string>
    <string name="nutriInfoTile">As consumers increasingly demand to know the nutritional value of what they eat and drink, European food production companies and large-scale caterers move towards adopting the Nutri-Score labelling system.</string>


    <string name="NutriScoreTitle">Nutri-Score – A Simple Science-Based Nutritional Value Labelling System for the Food Industry</string>
</resources>